Joseph L. Rauh Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part II: Legal File, 1926-1988 (Box 217-268)
  - Orlikow v. United States See also Containers 88, 274-282, and 287, same heading (Box 217)
    - Depositions
      - Gottlieb, Sidney, 1983, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box 223)
      - Grunberg, Frederic, 1988, (2 folders)
      - Hadwen, John G., 1986
      - Haskins, Caryl P., 1986
      - Helms, Richard M., 1983, (3 folders)
      - Hisey, Lloyd, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 224)
      - Huard, Jeannine, 1986
      - Joseph, David I., 1988
      - Lang, Wayne, 1988
      - Langleben, Moe, 1986
      - Lashbrook, Robert V., 1986
      - Laubinger, Frank H.
        - 1987
        - 1983 (Box 225)
      - Lifton, Robert Jay, 1988
      - Logie, Robert K., 1986
      - Lowy, Frederick Hans, 1988, (2 folders)
      - Mann, Alan M., 1988, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 226)
      - Morrow, Mary M., 1986, (2 folders)
      - Olson, Alice W., 1988
      - Orlikow, David, 1988
      - Orlikow, Velma, 1986, (2 folders)
      - Page, Jean Charles, 1986
      - Pasternak, Walter Paul, 1982
      - Rappeport, Jonas R., 1988, (4 folders) (Box 227)
      - Rhodes, David A., 1982
      - Rothman, David J., 1988, (2 folders)
      - Salzman, Leon L., 1988, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 228)
      - Schreck, Karralyn, 1988
      - Solandt, Omond, 1988
      - Stadler, Lyvia, 1986
      - Sternklar, Mrs. Terry, 1988
      - Termansen, Paul E., 1988, (2 folders)
      - Turner, Stansfield, 1983
      - Valenstein, Elliot S., 1988, (2 folders)
      - Weinstein, Harvey M., 1988, (2 folders) (Box 229)
      - Weinstein, Louis, 1986
      - Zimmerman, Catherine, 1988
      - Zimmerman, Rita, 1986
    - Documentary discovery
      - Cameron, D. Ewen, subpoena production, 1983
      - Defendant's production
        - First interrogatories
          - MKULTRA
            - General, 1975
            - Subprojects 68 and 60, 1953-1975
          - Olson, Frank R., death, 1953-1975
        - Gottlieb, Sidney, 1951-1955, (2 folders)
        - MKULTRA (Box 230)
          - Funding, 1983
          - Project, 1983, (2 folders)
        - Numbers
          - 13, 15, and 19-20, 1983
          - 21 (File: A/B, 5,115,"artichoke," 1983; A/B, 5,342-5,361--Morse, Allen, 1983)
      - Defendant's response
        - First interrogatories
          - MKULTRA, subproject 60, 1982
          - Olson, Frank R., death, 1982
        - Third set of interrogatories, 1952-1980, (2 folders)
      - Plaintiffs' (Box 231)
        - First request for production
          - Numbers
            - 1-2, MKULTRA, subprojects 68 and 60, 1982
            - 3, Frank R. Olson's death, 1982
            - 4, MKULTRA files destruction, 1982
            - 5-27, Donald O. Hebb security clearance, 1982
            - 31-32, MKULTRA, subproject 121 and Wittkower newsletter, 1982
            - 34-35, Donald O. Hebb security waiver and clandestine service instruction, 1982
            - 36-37, MKULTRA subjects notification and apology to Mrs. Frank R. Olson, 1982
            - 38, Rhodes study on communist control, 1982
            - 39, Psychological studies, 1982
            - 40, Human Ecology Fund reports, 1982
            - 53, Department of Health and Human Services regulations, 1982
            - 56-58, "Artichoke" documents, 1982
        - Huard, Jeannine, response to defendant's third set of interrogatories, 1988 (Box 232)
        - Langleben, Florence, response to defendant's fourth set of interrogatories, 1988
        - Logie, Robert K., response to defendant's third set of interrogatories, 1988
        - MKULTRA
          - Audits, 1955-1965
          - Funding, 1955-1967, undated, (2 folders)
          - Subproject 68, Freedom of Information Act documents, 1957-1960, undated
        - Orlikow, Velma, response to defendant's third set of interrogatories, 1988
        - Page, Jean Claude, response to defendant's third set of interrogatories, 1988
        - Stadler, Lyvia, response to defendant's third set of interrogatories, 1988
        - State Department, 1983
        - Weinstein, Louis, response to defendant's third set of interrogatories, 1988
        - Zimmerman, Rita, response to defendant's third set of interrogatories, 1988 (Box 233)
    - Exhibits
      - Defendant's
        - Medical records
          - Logie, Robert K., 1956-1986, (2 folders)
          - Stadler, Lyvia, 1957-1982, (2 folders)
        - Numbers
          - 1-9, 1953-1964
          - 10, 1952-1966, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 234)
          - 11-15, 1948-1987
          - 18-27, 1953-1960
          - 29, 1956
          - 30-43, 1954-1960
          - 44, 1951-1988, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 235)
          - 45, 1951-1988, (7 folders)
          - 46, 1957-1982, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 236)
          - 47, 1946-1982, (6 folders)
          - 48, 1956-1983, (5 folders) (Box 237)
          - 49, 1956-1988, (2 folders) (Box 238)
          - 50, 1952-1983, (2 folders)
          - 51-62, 1955-1963
          - 64-75, 1959-1961
          - 76, 1959-1982, (7 folders); (1 folder) (Box 239, Box 240)
          - 77-94, 1957-1960
          - 96-98, 1954-1978
          - 99, 1959-1962
          - 100-115, 1951-1988
        - Summary, 1988
        - Transcript, Morrow v. Royal Victoria Hospital, 1978
      - Plaintiffs'
        - Numbers
          - 67a-67l, 1955-1964
          - 68-70c, 1952-1961 (Box 241)
          - 71-80, 1948-1957
          - 81-96, 1951-1976
          - 97-107, 1952-1987
          - 108-112, 1957-1988
      - Weinstein, Harvey M., 1988
    - Expert materials, defendant's
      - Hisey, Lloyd
        - 1988
        - 1957-1983 (Box 242)
      - Mann, Alan M., 1959-1988, (3 folders)
      - Rappeport, Jonas R., 1988
      - Valenstein, Elliot S., 1950-1988, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 243)
    - Filing notice, defendant, George Cooper report, 1987, (2 folders)
    - Gottlieb, Sidney re Scott v. United States
      - Deposition, 1981
      - Statement, 1980
    - Informed consent materials, 1986, (2 folders) (Box 244)
    - Medical records
      - Huard, Jeannine
        - French, 1951-1958
        - General
          - Vol. 1, 1951-1968, (3 folders)
          - Vol. 2, 1951-1977, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 245)
        - Gravel, François, 1976-1986
        - Hôpital Du Sacre-Coeur, 1955
        - Hôpital Maisonneuve, 1961
        - Hôpital Sainte-Justine, 1988
        - Shanks, John, 1977-1987
      - Langleben, Florence
        - General, 1952-1983
        - Jewish General Hospital, 1964-1970
        - Levitsky, Peter, and Hollywood Memorial Hospital, 1967-1980
      - Logie, Robert K.
        - General, 1977-1983
        - Termansen, Paul E., 1984-1988, (1 folder) (Box 246)
      - Morrow, Mary M., 1960
      - Orlikow, Velma, 1951-1988, (2 folders)
      - Page, Jean Charles
        - Frechette, Robert, 1979-1988
        - Hôpital Des Laurentides, 1965-1966
        - Hôpital Du Sacre-Coeur, 1973-1986
        - Hôpital Notre-Dame, 1965
        - Hôpital Saint Jean-de-Dieu, 1960-1965
        - Institut Albert Prevost, 1957-1965, (1 folder) (Box 247)
      - Releases, plaintiffs, 1988
      - Stadler, Lyvia
        - General, 1957-1986, (3 folders)
        - Kovacs, Leslie, 1979-1988
      - Weinstein, Louis
        - General, 1956-1961
        - Jewish General Hospital, 1987
        - Klein, Michael, and Herzl Family Practice Centre, 1981-1987
      - Zimmerman, Rita
        - Goldberg, Erwin, and Orin Rosengren, 1972-1987
        - Hôpital Du Sacre-Coeur, 1946
        - Royal Victoria Hospital, 1946-1960, 1982, (3 folders) (Box 248)
        - Yufe, B., 1979-1986
    - Morrow, Mary M., 1978
    - Paul-Hus, Gilles, 1981
    - Plaintiffs' motion for summary judgment, evidence summary, undated
    - Pleadings
      - Index, undated
      - Numbers
        - 1, 1980-1981, (2 folders)
        - 2, 1982 (Box 249)
        - 3, 1983, (2 folders)
        - 4, 1983
        - 5, 1983, (2 folders)
        - 6, 1983, (2 folders)
        - 7, 1983, (2 folders) (Box 250)
        - 8, 1983, (2 folders)
        - 9, 1984-1985, (2 folders)
        - 10, 1986
        - 11, 1986, (2 folders) (Box 251)
        - 12, 1986
        - 13, 1986, (3 folders)
        - 13a, 1986, (2 folders)
        - 13b, 1986, (2 folders) (Box 252)
        - 13c-e, 1986, (5 folders)
        - 14, 1986
        - 15, 1986-1987 (Box 253)
        - 15a, undated
        - 16, 1987, (2 folders)
        - 17-19, 1988, (4 folders)
        - 20-21, 1988, (3 folders) (Box 254)
    - Tax records, plaintiffs', 1988, (5 folders) (Box 255)
    - Transcripts, 1983-1988, (3 folders)
    - Turner, James C., working file (Box 256)
      - Memoranda, 1984-1986, (2 folders)
      - Affidavits, 1986, (2 folders)
      - Ban, Thomas, 1978-1980
      - Barrett, Elizabeth, and Harold Blauer, 1952-1987, (2 folders)
      - Bexton, W. H., 1978
      - Biderman, Albert, 1978
      - Blumer, Ronald, 1986
      - Bos, Carlo, 1983-1988
      - Bothwell, Eva H., 1986
      - "Brainwashing"
        - General, 1956, 1978, undated, (2 folders)
        - Hearings, 1956 (Box 257)
      - Breggman, Peter, 1978
      - Cameron, D. Ewen
        - Central Intelligence Agency, funded papers, 1957-1967, 1978-1979
        - Funding, 1985
        - General, 1959-1980, (3 folders)
        - Published papers, 1956-1967, undated
      - Cameron, Duncan Hume, 1967, 1980-1983
      - Cameron, Jean, 1978
      - Canada, official secrets, 1981
      - Canadian embassy
        - General, 1977, 1983-1984
        - Materials provided to, 1984 (Box 258)
      - Canadian Mental Health Association, 1986
      - Center for National Security Studies v. Central Intelligence Agency, 1970-1973, undated
      - Cleghorn, Robert Allen
        - Deposition, 1988, undated, (4 folders)
        - General, 1978, 1986
      - Complaint
        - Central Intelligence Agency, documentary appendix, 1978, undated
        - General, 1981
      - Cooper, George, report, 1986, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box 259)
      - Cutler, Philip, 1978
      - Damages, 1988, undated
      - Day, Stacy B., 1956-1984
      - Deposition
        - Documents, exhibits, 1957-1965
        - Errata sheets, 1983-1986
      - Dongier, Maurice, 1957-1983 (Box 260)
      - Doyle, Brian B., 1986-1988
      - Duemling, Robert Werner, 1978-1979, 1986
      - Elmquist, Paul O., 1985-1988
      - Executive orders and Freedom of Information Act regulations, 1976, 1982
      - Frechette, Robert, 1988
      - Fund-raising
        - General, 1986-1988
        - J. Roderick MacArthur Foundation, 1986-1988
        - Philip M. Stern application, 1988
      - Gittinger, John W., deposition
        - Documents, 1955-1964, (2 folders)
        - General, 1983, (1 folder) (Box 261)
      - Glickman v. United States, 1983
      - Goldman, Philip, deposition, 1983
      - Gottlieb, Sidney
        - Deposition
          - Exhibits, 1953-1977, 1983, (2 folders)
          - General, 1981-1983, (3 folders)
          - Notes, 1983
      - Grunberg, Frederic, 1988
      - Hadwen, John G., 1979-1986
      - Harlow, Harry F., 1978 (Box 262)
      - Haskins, Caryl P., 1951, 1986
      - Hebb, Donald O., 1978-1982, undated
      - Helms, Richard M.
        - Exhibits, 1953-1963
        - General, 1975-1983
        - Outline and notes, 1983
        - President's Commission on Central Intelligence Agency Activities, testimony, 1975, (2 folders)
      - Heron, Woodburn, 1978
      - Hinkle, Lawrence E. (1918- ), 1983-1986
      - Hisey, Lloyd, 1983
      - Holt, Robert, 1978
      - Holt, William, 1978
      - Huard, Jeannine, Allan Memorial Institute records, 1951-1962, 1980-1983
      - Hulse, Stacy B., Jr., 1975-1984
      - Human Ecology Fund, Hungarians, 1956-1958
      - Joseph, David I., 1985-1988
      - Knaus, John K., 1980-1984
      - Kragie, Scott T., documents for authentication, 1957-1958, 1984-1986 (Box 263)
      - Lane, Peggy, 1978
      - Langleben, Florence, 1985-1986
      - Langleben, Wayne, 1983-1988
      - Lansdale, Herbert, 1978
      - Larsen, Alex F., 1984-1986
      - Lashbrook, Robert V., 1957-1959, 1977-1986
      - Laubinger, Frank H., deposition, exhibits, and notes, 1977-1983
      - Legal research
        - Document destruction, 1959, 1983, undated
        - Independent contractor, 1986, (3 folders)
        - Medical malpractice, 1926-1986, (1 folder) (Box 264)
      - Levisky, 1978
      - Levy, Leonard, 1960, 1978, undated
      - Lifton, Robert Jay
        - Deposition, 1986-1988
        - General, 1986
      - Lilly, John, 1978
      - Logie, Robert K., 1956-1960, 1986, undated
      - Lowy, Frederick Hans, deposition, 1988, undated
      - Lunde, Donald, 1988
      - Lysergic acid diethylamide (LSD), 1956-1967, 1986, undated
      - MacEachen, Allan J., affidavits, 1986
      - Mann, Alan M., deposition, 1988, undated
      - Marks, John D., affidavit, 1981
      - McGill University, Montreal, Canada, annual reports, 1953-1962
      - Melzak, Ronald, 1978
      - Metzenbaum, Howard M., 1984-1985
      - Moll, Albert, 1978
      - Monroe, James, 1961-1963, 1973-1977
      - Morrow, Mary M., records and proceedings, undated
      - Mueller, Herbert, 1983
      - Olson, Alice W., 1951-1955, 1976-1988 (Box 265)
      - Olson, Frank R., 1975-1978
      - Ontario Coalition to Stop Electroshock, 1984-1987, (2 folders)
      - Orlikow, David, deposition
        - Exhibits, 1956-1957, 1963-1964
        - General, 1978-1988
      - Orlikow, Velma and David
        - General, 1977-1983, (2 folders)
        - Interviews, 1978
      - Page, Jean Charles, writings, 1961, 1980
      - Page, L. G. M., and R. J. Russell, electrical convulsion therapy, 1948
      - Pasternak, Walter Paul, 1982
      - Pivnicki, Dimitrije, 1968-1985
      - Prince, Raymond, 1983
      - Psychological Assessment Associates, 1974-1977
      - Public Archives of Canada, 1982-1986 (Box 266)
      - Rappeport, Jonas R., medical summaries, 1988, undated
      - Retainer agreements, 1980-1986
      - Rhodes, David A., deposition, 1977-1982
      - Rockefeller Foundation, 1978
      - Roper, Peter, 1964-1966, 1978, 1983
      - Rothman, David J.
        - Deposition, 1986-1988
        - General, 1986-1988
      - Russell, R. J. See Container 265, Page, L. G. M.
      - Rubenstein, Leonard, 1962, 1979, undated
      - Salzman, Leon L.
        - Affidavits, 1986
        - Deposition, 1986-1988
      - Sander, Herman, 1978
      - Schwartzman, A. E., 1967, 1978, 1983
      - Scott v. Casey, 1981-1983
      - Shagass, Charles, 1951-1958, 1984
      - Sims v. Central Intelligence Agency, 1963, 1979-1982, (1 folder) (Box 267)
      - Society for the Investigation of Human Ecology, 1956-1965, undated
      - Sofaer, Abraham D., 1985
      - Solandt, Omond
        - Deposition, 1988
        - General, 1986-1988
      - Stadler, Lyvia, 1983, undated
      - Status hearings, 1983-1988
      - Summary judgment, oral argument, 1983-1987
      - Termansen, Paul E., records, 1984-1988, (2 folders)
      - Thornwell, James R., 1984
      - Trainor, Dorothy, 1978
      - Trip, Ottawa, Canada, 1985-1988
      - Turner, Stansfield, 1983-1988
      - United States apology to Canada, 1977-1985, (2 folders) (Box 268)
      - Valenstein, Elliot S., deposition, 1980
      - Vispo, Raul H., 1978
      - Warbasse, Anne, 1978
      - Warren, Janet
        - Huard, Jeannine, review of records, 1988
        - Interviews of plaintiffs, 1988
        - Orlikow, Velma, review of records, undated
      - Weinstein, Harvey M.
        - Affidavits, 1986-1988
        - American Psychiatric Association, 1959, undated
      - Wolff, Harold, 1930, 1954-1960, 1983
      - Zielinski, John, 1984
      - Zimmerman, Rita, medical records, 1966, 1977-1983
- Part III: Personal Correspondence, 1966-1992 (Box 269)
  Correspondence and memoranda between Rauh and his friends, acquaintances, and the public.
  - 1966-1992, undated, (2 folders) (Box 269)
- Part III: Subject File, 1928-1992 (Box 269-272)
  Correspondence, memoranda, legal papers, reports, notes, and printed matter.
  Arrangement is alphabetical by name of individual or organization, topic, or type of material.
  - Abortion, 1992 (Box 269)
  - Adams v. Bennett See Adams v. Cavazos
  - Adams v. Cavazos, 1987-1990
  - Brennan, William J. (1906-1997), 1957-1989
  - Carnes, Edward, 1992
  - Carswell, G. Harrold, 1970
  - Civil rights, 1991-1992, undated See also Containers 24-25, same heading
  - Civil Rights Act of 1991
    - 1990-1991
    - 1991, undated (Box 270)
  - Coffin, Frank M., 1992, (2 folders)
  - Democratic Party, 1977, 1992 See also Containers 28-33, same heading
  - District of Columbia School of Law, Washington, D.C., dean's position, 1987-1988, undated, (2 folders)
  - Fifth amendment constitutional rights, 1987 (Box 271)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H., 1964-1967, 1975, undated See also Container 36, same heading
  - Interview with Rauh, 1991
  - Jones, Lee, re William Remington book, 1986 See also Container 36, same heading
  - Judicial selections, 1988
  - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights, 1982, 1991-1992
  - Library of Congress, 1988
  - McGovern, George, presidential campaign, 1991
  - Miscellany, 1969-1974, 1991-1992, undated
  - Notes, undated
  - Nunn, Sam, presidential campaign, 1983-1987
  - Pollitt, Daniel H., 1955-1964, 1971-1975, 1981-1991, undated, (2 folders)
  - Rauh, John, Senate campaign, New Hampshire, 1989-1992
  - Reginald H. Zalles Social Justice Fund, 1977-1988, (2 folders)
  - Supreme Court, 1928, 1957, 1988-1992, undated, (2 folders) (Box 272)
  - Thomas, Clarence, Supreme Court nomination, 1981-1992, undated, (4 folders)
  - Tsongas, Paul E., 1980-1981, 1992
  - Youth Communication, Washington, D.C., 1990, undated
- Part III: Legal File, 1949-1990 (Box 273-282)
  Correspondence, memoranda, briefs, opinions, petitions, notes, reports, medical records, financial papers, and printed matter pertaining to Rauh's legal cases.
  Arranged alphabetically by case name, client name, or subject, with the majority of the files further arranged by type of material.
  - Dale, Chester H., Jr., 1985-1989 (Box 273)
  - International Association of Machinists v. Federal Election Commission 1979-1980, (5 folders)
    - 1981-1982, undated, (4 folders) (Box 274)
  - Miller, Arthur, undated See also Container 85, same heading
  - Orlikow v. United States See also Containers 88, 217-268, and 287, same heading
    - Appeal pursuant to 28 United States code 1292(b), 1987-1988, undated
    - Correspondence
      - 1978-1985
      - 1986-1989, undated, (2 folders) (Box 275)
    - Documentary discovery and related material
      - Cameron, D. Ewan, 1960-1964, 1980, undated
      - Central Intelligence Agency research
        - Bluebird/artichoke documents, 1950-1956, 1978, undated
        - General, 1953-1983, undated, (4 folders)
    - Evidence (Box 276)
      - General, 1957-1988, (3 folders)
      - Haskins, Caryl, exhibits, 1951-1986, undated
    - Federal Torts Claims Act, 1954, 1971, 1984, undated
    - Glickman, Stanley, 1986, undated
    - House of Commons, Canada, 1984-1988, (2 folders)
    - Pleadings (Box 277)
      - Background information, 1949, 1975, 1982-1986, undated
      - General
        - 1982-1987, (5 folders)
        - 1988
          - Jan.-July, (3 folders)
          - July-Oct., (2 folders) (Box 278)
        - 1989, undated, (3 folders)
      - List, undated
    - Research
      - Cooper, George, report, 1986, (2 folders)
      - General, 1986-1989, undated
    - Tax records (Box 279)
      - Huard, Jeannine, 1961-1988
      - Langleben, Florence, 1975-1987
      - Zimmerman, Rita, 1979-1987
    - Turner, James C., working file
      - Background information provided by David Orlikow, 1956-1988, undated
      - Documentary discovery, 1981-1988, undated
      - Expert witnesses, 1986
      - Logie, Robert K.
        - General, 1956-1964, 1979-1984, undated, (2 folders)
        - Insurance records, 1984-1987
      - Morrow, Mary, deposition notes, 1986 (Box 280)
      - Notes
        - Client interviews, 1986
        - Court, 1986-1987, undated
        - General
          - 1980-1985, (6 folders)
          - 1985-1988, (8 folders) (Box 281)
      - Page, Jean Charles, 1979-1983, undated
      - Peterzell, Jay, 1955-1956, 1978, 1985-1986
      - Student papers, 1986-1989 (Box 282)
    - Verifications and releases, 1988
    - Weinstein, Louis, 1956
  - Salzman, Leon, 1986
  - United Auto Workers, AFL/CIO See also Containers 97-116, same heading
    - Kamp, Joseph P., and Edward Rumley documents, 1949-1960, undated, (7 folders)
    - Tucker v. Bieber, 1990
  - United Mine Workers, 1972-1974 See also Containers 116-118, same heading
  - United Steelworkers of America v. Sadlowski, petition for rehearing, 1981 See also Containers 122-131, same heading
- Part III: Miscellany, 1940-1992 (Box 282-284)
  Correspondence, memoranda, articles, book reviews, letters to editors, speeches, printed matter, and other items.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of material or topic.
  - Awards and honors, 1987, undated (Box 282)
  - Biographical file, 1979-1992
  - Counsel to Labor Department, 1940 (Box 283)
  - Miscellany, 1991, undated
  - Speeches by Rauh
    - Miscellany, 1986-1991
    - Texts and related matter
      - 1950-1990, (8 folders)
      - 1990-1992, undated, (8 folders) (Box 284)
  - Writings
    - By Rauh
      - Articles, 1950-1991, (2 folders)
      - Book reviews, 1975, 1983-1984
      - Letters to editors, 1981-1982, undated
      - Miscellany, undated
    - By others, 1988-1992
- Part IV: Personal Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 285)
  Correspondence and memoranda between Rauh and his friends, acquaintances, and the public, including attachments.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent.
  - 1984-1986, (11 folders) (Box 285)
- Part IV: Subject File, 1928-1993 (Box 285-287)
  Correspondence, memoranda, legal papers, reports, speeches, notes, and printed matter.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of individual, organization, or topic.
  - Atomic energy, 1946 (Box 285)
  - Bork, Robert, Supreme Court nomination, 1987-1988
  - Cardozo, Benjamin N., 1928, 1936-1946, 1965, undated, (5 folders) (Box 286)
  - Civil Rights Act of 1990, 1990
  - Clark, Blair, 1983-1984
  - Cohen, Benjamin V., 1936-1946, 1983, undated
  - Democratic National Convention (1968), 1967-1968, 1984
  - Donahue, Elizabeth, 1976-1990
  - Dudley, Tilford E., 1990
  - Frankfurter, Felix, 1937-1964, 1973-1977, 1988-1993, undated, (5 folders)
  - Miscellany, 1986
  - National Organization for Women, 1990-1991 (Box 287)
  - Nunn, Guy, 1993
  - Pollitt, Daniel H., proposed law school, 1986-1992, undated
  - Powell, Adam Clayton (1908-1972), 1988
  - Rehnquist, William H., Supreme Court nomination for chief justice, 1986
  - Schlesinger, Arthur Meier (1917- ), 1978, 1989-1993
  - St. Barnabas College, Johannesburg, South Africa, 1993
  - Supreme Court, list of cases argued by Rauh, 1989
  - Thomas, Clarence, Supreme Court nomination, 1992
  - Union of American Hebrew Congregations, 1986
  - Wage and hour legislation, 1939-1942, undated, (6 folders)
- Part IV: Legal File, 1985-1994 (Box 287)
  Correspondence, memoranda, and printed matter pertaining to the case Orlikow v. United States.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Orlikow v. United States, 1985-1994 See also Containers 88, 217-268, 274-282, same heading (Box 287)
- Part IV: Miscellany, 1940-1993 (Box 287-289)
  Correspondence, memoranda, articles, book reviews, speeches, transcripts of oral history interviews, printed matter, and other items.
  - Awards and honors, 1985-1987 (Box 287)
  - Biographical file, 1976-1988, undated
  - Death of Rauh, 1992
    - Condolence letters
      - A-F, (3 folders)
      - G-Z, (9 folders) (Box 288)
      - Unidentified
    - Tributes
  - Oral history projects
    - Civil Rights Documentation Project, Howard University, Washington, D.C., 1967